Register to The Benny Goodman Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Band and Combo Arrangements
  - BULGAR AND OTHER BALKAN TYPE INVENTIONS, THE Carisi, Johnny, 4/1962 (Box 05, Folder 01)
    Score: last 2 pages only
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - BUT NOT FOR ME Karlin, Fred, 6/2/1960 (Box 05, Folder 02)
    BG No.: D227/404
  - BUT NOT FOR ME, 1959 (Box 05, Folder 03)
    BG No.: D227/14
    Score: second chorus only
    Vocal for Anita O'Day. Complete.
  - BUT NOT FOR ME Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 05, Folder 04)
    BG No.: F132/310
    Later recopy.
  - BUTTONS AND BOWS Sauter, Eddie, 1945 (Box 05, Folder 05)
    BG No.: A245/127
  - BYE BYE BLACKBIRD Bunch, John, 1962 (Box 05, Folder 06)
    BG No.: 277/Fl
  - BYE BYE BLUES Williams, Mary Lou, 1948 (Box 05, Folder 07)
    BG No.: B391
    Parts: GBD
  - C JAM BLUES McFarland, Gary, 4/1962 (Box 05, Folder 08)
    BG No.: D434/288
  - CABARET, 1969 (Box 5A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: G106/C1
  - CALYPSO MAN (Box 5A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: 184/C1
  - CAN'T GET OUT OF THIS MOOD Henderson, Fletcher, c.1939 (Box 5A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: A348
  - CAN'T WE BE FRIENDS Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 5A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: A349/C2/22/38
  - CAN'T WE BE FRIENDS? Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 5A, Folder 12A)
    BG No.: A349/34
  - CANADIAN CAPERS Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 5A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: A321
  - CANTEEN BOUNCE Sauter, Eddie, 1943 (Box 5A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: A322
  - CAPRICE XXIV - PAGANINI Martin, Skip, 9/13/1941 (Box 5A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: C246/C3
    Includes photocopies of entire arrangement (parts and score). Complete.
  - CARELESS Henderson, Fletcher (Box 5A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: C2/115
  - CARELESS Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 09)
  - CARIOCA Pleis, Jack, 9/16/1946 (Box 5A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: B228
  - CAROLINA IN THE MORNING, 1939 (Box 5A, Folder 18)
    BG No.: C143/137
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Clarinet parts differ slightly.
  - CAUSE MY BABY SAYS IT'S SO Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 5A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: A166/202
  - CHARADE Newsom, Tommy, 6/1964 (Box 5B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: F102
    Parts: cl(3)/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - CHARLOT PREMIER Legrand, Michel, 10/1959 (Box 5B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: D230
  - CHEROKEE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 5B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: C325/44A
    Parts: saxAATTB(2)/tpt1-4(2)/tbn1-3/PGB
    Tpt4 and saxB; are added parts.
  - CHICAGO Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 5B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: C324/116
  - CHICAGO Henderson, Fletcher, 1934 (Box 5B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: C324/C4
  - CHICAGO Henderson, Fletcher, 1934 (Box 5B, Folder 24A)
    BG No.: 23
  - CHINATOWN Bone, Red, 1935 (Box 5B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A240/21/291
  - CHONK CHARLIE CHONK Mundy, Jimmy, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    BG No.: C280/65A
    Parts: cl/saxTTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-2/PGB
    Also known as "Solo Flight".
  - CHRISTOLA Henderson, Horace, 1935 (Box 5B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: A234
  - CHURCHILL'S PORTRAIT Brant, Henry, 1945 (Box 5B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: C267/A233
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1,3-4/PGBD/horn
  - CIRIBIRIBIN Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 5C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: A23
    Score: incomplete-original and photocopy
  - CLAP YOUR HANDS Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 5C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: A66/363
  - CLARINADE (Box 5C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: B371/41
    Parts: cl/PGBDV
    Based on 1945 Mel Powell composition.
  - CLARINADE, 1959 (Box 5C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: G130
    Parts: cl/saxT/tbn/PGBD/rhythm lead sheet(3)
  - CLARINADE, 1960 (Box 5C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: B371/31
    Parts: saxT/tpt/tbn/GBV/fl
  - CLARINADE Powell, Mel, 1945 (Box 5C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: B137/C5
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn2-3/PGBD
    All parts are photocopies.
  - CLARINADE, 1947 (Box 5C, Folder 34)
    Score: missing first page
    Combo arrangement of 1945 Mel Powell composition.
  - CLARINET A LA KING Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 06, Folder 01)
    BG No.: D38/C6
    Clarinet parts differ slightly. These parts are from several different copies.
  - CLARINET MARMALADE Bone, Red, 1935 (Box 06, Folder 02)
    BG No.: A239/15/294/107
  - CLARINET MARMALADE Kincaide, Deane, 1946 (Box 06, Folder 03)
    BG No.: A239
  - CLARINETTA Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 06, Folder 04)
    BG No.: B133
  - CLIMB EVERY MOUNTAIN Karlin, Fred, 1959 (Box 06, Folder 05)
    BG No.: D217/17
    Parts: cl/PGBV
  - CLOSE AS PAGES IN A BOOK Sauter, Eddie, 1945 (Box 06, Folder 06)
    BG No.: A132
  - CLOSE AS PAGES IN A BOOK Henderson, Fletcher, 1945 (Box 06, Folder 07)
    BG No.: C269/4
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/GBD
  - CLOSE YOUR EYES Newsom, Tommy, 4/1963 (Box 06, Folder 08)
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/"rhythm"
  - CLOSING BILLBOARD Burns, Ralph (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - COME ON YOU MOON Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 06, Folder 09)
    BG No.: 331
  - COME RAIN OR COME SHINE Wilkinson, Ralph, 1946 (Box 06, Folder 10)
    BG No.: B134
  - COME RAIN OR SHINE, 1959 (Box 06, Folder 11)
    BG No.: D228/407
    Includes a sketch of bass part. Vocal for Anita O'Day. Complete.
  - COMING HOME Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 6A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: 72
  - COMPLAININ' Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 6A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: A160
    Includes sheet music on which arrangement was based.
  - CONVERSATION Williams, Mary Lou, 1947 (Box 6A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: C142
  - COO KOO (Box 6A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: C141/99
  - COOKIE HOUSE Wootten, Red, 9/22/1960 (Box 6A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: D57
  - COOKIN' ONE UP, 1948 (Box 6A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: 127
    Parts: cl/GBD
    Drum part from different copy.
  - COOKIN' ONE UP Powell, Mel, 1948 (Box 6A, Folder 18)
    Parts: saxT/tpt/PBV
  - COOT Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 6A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: C305
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn2/PBD
    Tpt1 labeled "Cootie". Also includes extra incomplete bass part.
  - COPPER COLORED GAL Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 6A, Folder 20)
    BG No.: A241/220/130
  - COQUETTE Jenkins, Gordon, 4-5/1976 (Box 6A, Folder 21)
    BG No.: G147
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAAT(2)TB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/PGBD/chords only rhythm
    All parts are photocopies except: saxA1/tpt1/tbn3/P. Complete.
  - CORN SILK Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 6B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: B135/251E/32A
  - CORN SILK Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 6B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: 37A
    This arrangement differs slightly from other Sauter version.
  - COULD BE Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 6B, Folder 24)
  - COULD YOU PASS IN LOVE? Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 6B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: Al 57/696
  - COW COW BOOGIE, 1942 (Box 6B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: C131/1A
  - COWBOY FROM BROOKLYN Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 6B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: A161/712
  - COZY Matthews, Dave, 1945 (Box 6B, Folder 28)
    BG No.: A165/804
  - CRAZY LITTLE TUNE Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 6B, Folder 29)
    BG No.: C138
  - CRAZY RHYTHM Lipman, Joe, 1934 (Box 6B, Folder 30)
    BG No.: A133/48
  - CRAZY RHYTHM Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 6C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: A133/32/45/413B
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB(2)/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - CREDO Ogerman, Claus, 1969 (Box 6C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: GB/C7
  - CRYING MY HEART OUT FOR YOU Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 6C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: D30/5
    Parts: cl/saxAT(-A2,T1)/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - CU TU GU RU Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 6C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: A164
  - DADDY'S BOY Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 6C, Folder 35)
    BG No.: A299
  - DAILY BLUES, 1946 (Box 6C, Folder 36)
    BG No.: A351/70
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt2-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - DANCING IN THE DARK Kincaide, Deane, 1958 (Box 6D, Folder 37)
    BG No.: D40
  - DARN THAT DREAM Stegmeyer, Bill, 6/1960 (Box 6D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: D324/52
  - DAY I LET YOU GET AWAY, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 6D, Folder 39)
    BG No.: B364
  - DAY I LET YOU GET AWAY, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 6D, Folder 40)
    BG No.: A380/464.5
    Score: condensed
  - DEAR DAVE McGuffie, Bill, 1970 (Box 6D, Folder 41)
    BG No.: D3
    Parts: saxAT/tpt1-3/tbn1,3-4/P(3)GBD
  - DEAR OLD SOUTHLAND Henderson, Horace, 1935 (Box 6D, Folder 42)
    BG No.: A134
    Parts: saxB
  - DEAR OLD SOUTHLAND Henderson, Horace, 1935 (Box 6D, Folder 42A)
    BG No.: 44
  - DEED I DO Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 6E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: D58/234
    Parts: cl/saxTB/tpt/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - DEEP IN THE HEART OF TEXAS, 1942 (Box 6E, Folder 44)
    BG No.: C139/72A
  - DELIA GONE Evans, Gil, 1956 (Box 6E, Folder 45)
    BG No.: C55/182A
    Vocal arrangement. Complete.
  - DESIGN FOR JIVIN', 1941 (Box 6E, Folder 46)
    BG No.: A296
  - DEVIL MAY CARE Hallenbeck, Ralph, 1940 (Box 6E, Folder 47)
    BG No.: A295/300
    Parts: tbn3
  - DEVIL MAY CARE Sauter, Eddie, 1940 (Box 6E, Folder 48)
    BG No.: A295
  - DID I REMEMBER Gutesha, Bobby, 1959 (Box 07, Folder 01)
    BG No.: D64/253
  - DID YOU MEAN IT Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 07, Folder 02)
    BG No.: C306/261
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGB
  - DIGA DIGA DO Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 07, Folder 03)
    BG No.: A353/70
  - DING DONG DADDY Murphy, Spud, 3/27/1935 (Box 07, Folder 04)
    BG No.: D33/146
    Parts: tbn1-2
  - DIXIELAND BAND Kincaide, Deane, 1934 (Box 07, Folder 05)
    BG No.: C227
    This is a recopy and expansion from the 1950's. There are no original parts.
  - DIXIELAND ONE-STEP Fontaine, Bill (Box 07, Folder 06)
    BG No.: A6
  - DIZZY FINGERS Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 07, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A120/C263
    Solo el part is in C. Also, all sax parts double either cl or bscl. Cl and rhythm parts are adapted from other copies. Complete.
  - DIZZY FINGERS Powell, Mel, 1947 (Box 07, Folder 08)
    BG No.: D201
    Parts: fl1-2/ob1-2/cl1-2/bsn1-2
    Arrangement for woodwinds to accompany original solo cl part.
  - DIZZY SPELLS (Box 07, Folder 09)
    Parts: cl/tbn/PBDV
  - DO NOTHIN' Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 7A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: D350/67
  - DO YOU CARE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 7A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B223
  - DO YOU STILL LOVE ME Thompson, Johnny, 1942 (Box 7A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: A300/96A
  - DO-RE-MI Karlin, Fred, 11/13/1959 (Box 7A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: D215/18
  - DOCTOR, LAWYER, INDIAN-CHIEF, 1946 (Box 7A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: C361
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-2,4/tbn1,3/PGBD
  - DODGING A DIVORCEE Murphy, Spud, 1934 (Box 7A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: C359/141
    SaxA2 is incomplete.
  - DOLLY Newsom, Tommy, 6/1964 (Box 7A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: F104
  - DON'T BE THAT WAY Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 7A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: C124/D1
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/GB
  - DON'T BE THAT WAY Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 7A, Folder 18)
    Renumbered, recopied and expanded (i.e. tpt4) from other version labeled D1.
  - DON'T BE THAT WAY Sampson, Edgar (Box 7A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: C124/13
    Score: yes, including 2 pg. insert labeled "DBTW-recopy"
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-2/PGBD
    Includes score(2) of "added" PARTS
  - DON'T BE THAT WAY Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 7B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: C339/11
    Original parts (saxA1TT/tpt1-2/tbn1-2) and pencil recopies make this set. All parts include added 8 measure tag.
  - DON'T BE THAT WAY Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 7B, Folder 20A)
    BG No.: 2
  - DON'T BLAME ME Allen, Shorty, 1946 (Box 7B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: A117/100
  - DON'T BLAME ME Henderson, Fletcher, 1945 (Box 7B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: A117/15
  - DON'T BLAME ME (Box 7B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: A117/25
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-2,4/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - DON'T CRY BABY Homer, Ben (Box 7B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: A298
  - DON'T GET AROUND MUCH ANYMORE, 1969 (Box 7B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: G125
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/PGBD
    Parts included for six brass version.
  - DON'T GET AROUND MUCH ANYMORE Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 7B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: D349/65
  - DON'T HAVE TO TELL NOBODY, c.1948 (Box 7B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: C132/161
    Parts: 'cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - DON'T MENTION LOVE TO ME Shapiro, Harold, 2/24/1942 (Box 7B, Folder 28)
    BG No.: B134/44A
  - DON'T TAKE YOUR LOVE FROM ME Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 7B, Folder 29)
    BG No.: B138
  - DONNA LEE Williams, Mary Lou, 1948 (Box 7B, Folder 30)
    BG No.: 141
    Parts: saxT/PGBD
  - DORSEY MEDLEY Feller, Sid, 4/10/1958 (Box 7C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: D342/204
    Medley of "Contrasts" and "Opus I". Complete.
  - DOUBLE ACTION Williams, George, 1958 (Box 7C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: B382/219
  - DOUBLE TROUBLE Henderson, Fletcher, c.1936 (Box 7C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: B239
  - DOUBLE TROUBLE Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 7C, Folder 33A)
    BG No.: 32
  - DOWN BY THE RIVER Kincaide, Deane, 1935 (Box 7C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: A254/170
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - DOWN SOUTH CAMP MEETING Henderson, Fletcher (Box 08, Folder 01)
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
    All parts photocopies. These are NOT from the original arrangement; this is a transcription from record for Glenn Gray.
  - DOWN SOUTH CAMP MEETING Henderson, Fletcher (Box 08, Folder 1A)
    BG No.: 6/D2/B37
    Photocopies only
  - DREAM A LITTLE DREAM OF ME (Box 08, Folder 02)
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/PGBD
  - DREAM A LITTLE DREAM OF ME, 1958 (Box 08, Folder 03)
    BG No.: B266/195
    Parts: cl/saxAAT7B/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - DREAM A LITTLE DREAM OF ME White, Johnny, 1946 (Box 08, Folder 04)
    BG No.: B226
  - DREAMIN' AND SWINGIN' Di Novi, Gene, 3/1959 (Box 08, Folder 05)
    BG No.: D301/40
  - DREAMING OUT LOUD Sauter, Eddie, 1940 (Box 08, Folder 06)
    BG No.: B206
  - DREAMY EYES Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 8A, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A255/194
  - DRIP DROP Thompson, Johnny, 1943 (Box 8A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: A297
    Parts: saxBs
  - DRUMS IN MY HEART Feller, Sid, 1958 (Box 8A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: B372/248
    Parts: cl/saxB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD/voca1
  - E BOP 0 LEE BOP Clayton, Buck, 1949 (Box 8A, Folder 10)
  - EARFUL OF MUSIC Carter, Benny, 1934 (Box 8A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: A282/50
  - EARL, THE Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 8A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: 111/B4
    Only piano part is original. All other parts are photocopies.
  - EARLY AUTUMN Lipman, Joe, 9/1961 (Box 8A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: D409/255
  - EAST OF THE SUN Roumanis, George, 1957 (Box 8A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: D44/190
    Also includes incomplete condensed score sketch labeled "Urbie". Complete.
  - EASY DOES IT Clayton, Buck, 1939 (Box 8A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: D24/298
    Arrangement recorded by Count Basie in 1939.
  - EASY TO LOVE Cohn, Al, 1955 (Box 8A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: C376
    Parts: cl/tpt/tbn/PBD
  - EGGHEAD O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 01, Folder 21)
    Score: see reverse side of "All the Way Choo Choo", pp. 1-3
    Score from rehearsal letter G only.
  - EIGHT NINE TEN Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 8B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: A256
  - ELTEEB AINAM McGuffie, Bill, 1969 (Box 8B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: G18/El
    Also includes parts for three trombone arrangement. These parts do not match the score. Complete.
  - EMBRACEABLE YOU Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 8B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: C218/66/B302
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-2/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - EMBRACEABLE YOU - S'WONDERFUL Carisi, Johnny, 4/1962 (Box 8B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: F22/295
    Parts: cl/saxAT/tpt/tbn/PGBD
    Also includes entire set of parts for B major version. Complete.
  - ENCHANTED SHACK White, Johnny, 1946 (Box 8B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: A258
  - EV'RY DAY Hensel, Wes, 2/1960 (Box 8B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: D414
    Parts: cl/saxAT/tpt/tbn/PGB
  - EVERY LITTLE MOMENT Murphy, Spud, 4/30/1935 (Box 8B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: C366/177
  - EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 8B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: A283
  - EVERY SUNDAY AFTERNOON Henderson, Fletcher, 1940 (Box 8B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A36/302/527
  - EVERYTHING I LOVE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 8C, Folder 26)
    BG No.: B139/5A
    Parts: saxTTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGB
    Original parts. Six measures at rehearsal B scratched out in all 52 parts; re-write (not corresponding to score) found at end.
  - EVERYTHING I LOVE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 8C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: B139/267
    Score: (see other arrangement)
    This is a recopy. Parts follow score (BG no.B139/5A with other arrangement) at rehearsal B and make a complete set.
  - EVERYTHING I'VE GOT BELONGS TO YOU (Box 8C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: C364/A118
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - EVERYTHING I'VE GOT BELONGS TO YOU Powell, Mel, 1947 (Box 8C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: 131/A118
  - EVERYTHING I'VE GOT BELONGS TO YOU Burns, Ralph, 1947 (Box 8C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: C153/120
  - EVERYTHING IS OKEY DOKEY Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 8C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: A55/618/35
  - EVERYTHING YOU SAID CAME TRUE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 8C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: A281/76
  - EVERYTHING'S IN RHYTHM WITH MY HEART Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 8C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: B340
  - EVERYTIME WE SAY GOODBYE Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 8C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: B341
  - EXIT Henderson, Horace (Box 8C, Folder 35)
    BG No.: B140
  - FABLE OF THE ROSE, THE Sauter, Eddie (Box 8C, Folder 36)
    BG No.: B205
  - FALLING IN LOVE Burns, Ralph, 5/1963 (Box 8C, Folder 37)
    BG No.: F32/9
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/PBDV
  - FARE THEE WELL, ANNABELLE, 1934 (Box 8C, Folder 38)
    BG No.: C40/36
    Trumpet parts are marked to be played on cornet.
  - FARE WELL MY LOVE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 8C, Folder 39)
    BG No.: B335
  - FAREWELL BLUES Murphy, Spud, 3/22/1935 (Box 8D, Folder 40)
    BG No.: B342
    Parts: tpt2
  - FASCINATING RHYTHM Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 8D, Folder 41)
    BG No.: A355/Fl
    Original parts.
  - FASCINATING RHYTHM (Box 8D, Folder 42)
    Parts: cl/GB
    Clarinet part marked "piano/conductor/control booth".
  - FEATHERS Bunch, John, 5/1962 (Box 8C, Folder 43)
    BG No.: F2/297
  - FEELING IS GONE, THE Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 09, Folder 01)
    BG No.: A381/11
  - FIDDLER MEDLEY Newsom, Tommy, 12/1965 (Box 09, Folder 02)
    BG No.: F112/F2
  - FILTHY McNASTY Bryant, Bobby, 5/1962 (Box 09, Folder 03)
    BG No.: D248/292
  - FINALE O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 09, Folder 04)
    BG No.: B345
    Parts: cl/saxATTB(-A2)/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/GBD
  - FINALE O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 09, Folder 05)
    Parts: cl/saxATTB(-A2)/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Guitar part is incomplete.
  - FINE AND DANDY Johnson, Budd, 1956 (Box 09, Folder 06)
    BG No.: A354/174
  - FINE AND DANDY Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 9A, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A354/114
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1,3/PGBD/horn
  - FINE ROMANCE, A Hyman, Dick, 6/21/1960 (Box 9A, Folder 08)
    BG No.: D316/47
  - FINE ROMANCE, A Feller, Sid, 4/10/1958 (Box 9A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: D207/207
    Arrangement for vocal duet. Complete.
  - FIVE FOOT TWO O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 9A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: B343
  - FIVE O'CLOCK WHISTLE Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 9A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B1 41/13A
  - FLAT FOOT FLOOGIE, THE Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 9A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: A382/30
  - FLIPPANT FLURRY Ellington, Duke, 1946 (Box 9A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: C264/A57
    Parts: cl/saxAATB(-T1)/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
    Also includes cl/rhythm lead sheet that is a shorter arrangement than the big band parts (marked A57).
  - FLYING HOME Martin, Skip, 1941 (Box 9B, Folder 14)
    BG No.: C228/85/33A
  - FOG HORN Thompson, Johnny, 1943 (Box 9B, Folder 15)
    BG No.: D36/95A/326
    Parts: cl/saxAATTBBs/tpt1-3/tbn2/PGD
  - FONTAINBLEAU Dameron, Tadd, 5/14/1962 (Box 9B, Folder 16)
    BG No.: D444/297
  - FOOLS FALL IN LOVE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 9B, Folder 17)
    BG No.: B338
  - FOR EVERY MAN (THERE'S A WOMAN), 1948 (Box 9B, Folder 18)
    BG No.: C31/118
    Parts: cl2/saxT/PGBD
    Cl part marked "Stanly"; saxT marked "Wardell".
  - FOR ME AND MY GAL Thompson, Johnny, 1943 (Box 9B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: C32/64A
    Parts: cl/saxAAT7B/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
  - FOUR BROTHERS, 1959 (Box 9B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: D225/17
    Vocal arrangement for Anita O'Day. Complete.
  - FRALICH IN SWING, 1939 (Box 9B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: 96
    Same arrangement penciled on the back of all parts in A. See "And the Angels Sing" for same music.
  - FRALICH IN SWING (ZIGGY'S TUNE) (Box 9B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: B365/34
    This is a 1945 recopy of the 1939 arrangement. Includes extra sax parts transposed to A.
  - FRENESI Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 9B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: B142/22A
    Parts: cl/saxTB(-T2)/tpt1-3/PB
    SaxB and P parts are incomplete. On the back of saxB, part, there is an incomplete cl part to "Down South Camp Meetin'".
  - FRENESI Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 9B, Folder 24)
  - FRENESI Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 9C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: B142
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-3(2)/PGBD
    Later recopy of original Henderson arrangement. Tbn3 parts from different copies.
  - FRENESI Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 9C, Folder 25A)
    BG No.: 46/112
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGB
    Parts are in Henderson's own hand. G is a photocopy.
  - FRESH FISH O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 9C, Folder 26)
    BG No.: B344
  - FRIEND BEN Thompson, Johnny, 1946 (Box 9C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: A338
  - FROM ANOTHER WORLD Feller, Sid, 1958 (Box 9C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: C119
    Parts: cl/saxB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD/vocal
  - FROM THE TOP OF YOUR HEAD, c.1958 (Box 9C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: C120/22
  - FUNNY THAT WAY, 1948 (Box 9C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: 121
  - GEE, BUT YOU'RE SWELL Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 9C, Folder 31)
    BG No.: 73
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/GB
  - GENTLE BEN Jenkins, Gordon, 1976 (Box 9C, Folder 32)
    BG No.: G144
    Parts: cl(3)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/P(2)GBD
    SaxA1 doubles flute. Complete.
  - GEORGIA JUBILEE Schutt, Arthur, 1934 (Box 9C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: D14
    Parts: saxAA/tpt2-3/tbn1-2/PGBD
    Piano part serves as condensed score.
  - GERSHWIN MEDLEY (Box 9D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: G110
    Parts: cl/saxATTB(-A1)/tpt2-3/tbn1-3
  - GERSHWIN MEDLEY Lipman, Joe, 5/8/1962 (Box 9D, Folder 35)
    BG No.: D437/270
    "How Long Has This Been Going On", "Who Cares", "Summertime", "Nice Work If You Can Get It" and "Fascinatin' Rhythm". Complete
  - GET HAPPY Powell, Mel, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 01)
    BG No.: D348/21
    Includes pencil sketch sheet.
  - GET HAPPY Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 02)
    BG No.: D348/414
  - GET HAPPY Murphy, Spud, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 03)
    BG No.: A339/61
  - GET RHYTHM IN YOUR FEET Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 04)
    BG No.: A340/32
  - GET YOURSELF ANOTHER FOOL, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 05)
    BG No.: B351
  - GET YOURSELF ANOTHER FOOL O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 06)
    BG No.: B351/240
  - GID-DAP NAPOLEON Kincaide, Deane, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 07)
    BG No.: C123
    Score: original and short arrangement from m.53 to end
    Includes solo part marked "Louie" (Armstrong). All parts have inserts for long arrangement (see scores), except piano and guitar.
  - GILLY (Box 10, Folder 08)
    BG No.: D319
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/tbn/PGBDV
    "Head arrangement" notated by Bob Wilbur 10/1959. Complete.
  - GLORY OF LOVE, THE Murphy, Spud, 1936 (Box 10A, Folder 09)
    BG No.: A145/T3
  - GLORY OF LOVE, THE (Box 10A, Folder 10)
    BG No.: A145/36
    Key: B
  - GONE Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 10A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: B349
  - GONNA GOD, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 10A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: A383/182
  - GOOD EVENIN', GOOD LOOKIN' Mundy, Jimmy, 1941 (Box 10A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: C144/11A
  - GOODBYE Stegmeyer, Bill, 1961 (Box 10A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: D347/2A
    Parts: saxAT/tbn/PGDV
  - GOODBYE O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 10A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: B352/228
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-2/PBD/vocal quintet
  - GOODBYE (Box 10A, Folder 16)
    Parts: cl(2)/saxTTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/PD
    Transcribed from record for Glenn Gray; NOT from original arrangement.
  - GOODBYE (Box 10A, Folder 17)
  - GOODBYE McEachern, Murray, 1960 (Box 10A, Folder 18)
  - GOODBYE, 1959 (Box 10A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: D347/2
    SaxA doubles flute.
  - GOODBYE (Box 10A, Folder 20)
    BG No.: A276/G1
    Score: "duplicated from recording" (2, slightly different)
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-2(2)3-4/tbn1-3/PGD